<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE ulr PUBLIC "-//UniLang//Universal Language Resource 1.9 (Language-Specific Subfile)//EN"
  "http://dev.unilang.org/docs/ulr1.9_sub.dtd">
<ulr id="paul2" version="1.9" baselang="en">
	<entries>
		<entry id="title">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">Paul 2</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="description">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">Paul lands and finds a hotel - 2</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="1">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">The flight took a few hours. Paul read a magazine for a short time. He took a nap after finishing with the magazine. When Paul woke again, the plane was preparing to land.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="2">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">The captain spoke over the speakers. &quot;We are preparing to land. Please fasten your seatbelts.&quot; Paul fastend his seatbelt. The man sitting next to him did too. The plane descended rapidly, then landed.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="3">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">Once the plane had parked at the airport, people started getting up to get their luggage and leave the plane.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="4">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">&quot;Good-bye,&quot; the stewardess told him as he passed her on the way out. &quot;We hope you had a good flight.&quot; Paul nodded, then left the plane with the other passengers.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="5">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">The airport was very busy, and he hurried to get his luggage. He waited at the luggage carousel for his bag to appear. He saw it when it passed him, and he picked it up.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="6">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">Paul took his bag and walked outside the airport. He saw there was a bus going to a hotel. He walked to the bus and got on. The driver stopped him.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="7">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">&quot;You have to pay for the ride,&quot; he told Paul.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="8">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">&quot;How much does it cost?&quot; Paul asked. The bus driver told him, and Paul pulled out some coins. He dropped the proper amount into the fare box and found a place to sit.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="9">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">Soon, the bus arrived at a hotel, and Paul got off. He walked into the hotel. There was a woman working at the desk.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="10">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">&quot;Can I help you?&quot; she asked Paul.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="11">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">&quot;Yes,&quot; Paul answered. &quot;I would like a single room with a shower, please.&quot;</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="12">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">&quot;Please sign the register,&quot; the clerk told him. Paul signed his name, and the clerk gave him his key. He looked at it, and saw he was in room 213. He thanked the clerk, picked up his bag, and headed towards the elevator.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="13">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">When he arrived on his floor, he left the elevator and walked down the hall. He heard a radio playing in one of the rooms as he looked for his own room. As he found the door to his room, he heard a few words clearly from the radio. He heard &quot;community&quot; and &quot;freaks&quot;, which didn't make any sense. Then he heard the word &quot;UniLang&quot;. He remembered the woman on the plane had a shirt on that said &quot;UniLang&quot;. Paul still didn't know what that was. He unlocked the door to his room and entered.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="14">
			<attrib type="orth" author="Abavagada">The room was small, but comfortable. He put his bag on a chair, then went to the window and looked out. He smiled as he looked out over the city, but then he remembered that word again. He had to find out what this &quot;UniLang&quot; was.</attrib>
		</entry>
	</entries>
</ulr>