<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE ulr PUBLIC "-//UniLang//Universal Language Resource 1.9 (Language-Specific Subfile)//EN"
  "http://dev.unilang.org/docs/ulr1.9_sub.dtd">
<ulr id="rapunzel" version="1.9" baselang="en">
	<entries>
		<entry id="title">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236706954">Rapunzel</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="description">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236706954">The classic fairy tale from the Grimm Brothers</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236709788">There once lived a man and his wife, who had long wished for a child, but in vain.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706360640">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236709788">At the back of their house, there was a little window which overlooked a beautiful garden full of the finest vegetables and flowers; but there was a high wall all round it, and no one ventured into it, for it belonged to a witch of great might, and of whom all the world was afraid.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706391690">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236709788">One day that the wife was standing at the window, and looking into the garden, she saw a bed filled with the finest rampion; and it looked so fresh and green that she began to wish for some; and at length she longed for it greatly. This went on for days, and as she knew she could not get the rampion, she pined away, and grew pale and miserable.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706424189">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236709788">Then the man was uneasy, and asked, “What is the matter, dear wife?”</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236708743771">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236709788">“Oh,” answered she, “I shall die unless I can have some of that rampion to eat that grows in the garden at the back of our house.”</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236708765421">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236709788">The man, who loved her very much, thought to himself, “Rather than lose my wife I will get some rampion, cost what it will.”</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706446753">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236706954">At twilight, he clambered down over the wall into the garden of the enchantress, hastily clutched a handful of rampion, and took it to his wife.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706467727">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236706954">She at once made herself a salad of it, and ate it greedily. It tasted so good to her--so very good, that the next day she longed for it three times as much as before.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706485365">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236706954">If he was to have any rest, her husband must once more descend into the garden.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706506528">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236706954">In the gloom of evening therefore, he let himself down again; but when he had clambered down the wall he was terribly afraid, for he saw the enchantress standing before him.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706524291">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236706954">'How can you dare,' said she with angry look, 'descend into my garden and steal my rampion like a thief? You shall suffer for it!'</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706541566">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236709788">'Ah,' answered he, 'let mercy take the place of justice, I only made up my mind to do it out of necessity.</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236709296910">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236709788">My wife saw your rampion from the window, and felt such a longing for it that she would have died if she had not got some to eat.'</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706588379">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236707021">Then the enchantress allowed her anger to be softened, and said to him: 'If the case be as you say, I will allow you to take away with you as much rampion as you will, only I make one condition, you must give me the child which your wife will bring into the world; it shall be well treated, and I will care for it like a mother.'</attrib>
		</entry>
		<entry id="e1236706607167">
			<attrib type="orth" author="13070" lastmodified="1236707021">The man, in his terror, consented to everything, and when the woman was brought to bed, the enchantress appeared at once, gave the child the name of Rapunzel, and took it away with her.</attrib>
		</entry>
	</entries>
</ulr>